Hi this is PC Rodger and on this short video I want to show you how you can save a webpage like this
Is homepage of pcrichard.com to a single-file some of you may be aware of the. MHT
He file for the. Mhtml file where you can do this
It's not a default option on Chrome or Firefox you might remember from Internet Explorer but who uses
That and that's a dead program anyway right
Well with chrome is not too hard to do with Firefox is actually a add-on that you have to get
With chrome is pretty easy and I will show you normally when you go to save a webpage like this you
You have
The two options of web page HTML only and it would just get one file but it doesn't end
Include all the graphics or any files that are required to help make up that page or what page can play
What kind of a messy subdirectory or folder with a lot of files in it and
And it's not as bad as cleaning need so it's nice to be able to it in a single-file which is which is
Almost perfect not quite but almost
And what, says he will just open another tab here
What type in Chrome colon slash slash flag so get this page here and let's just ask
Pro FM find
Multi pin mhtml
And you can see this option here save page as an HTML what quick and able
And then you simply have to restart Chrome
And now when you select save page as
Hand control s and save as a shortcut for that
You say that there are three options
What's the default actually being webpage single file
And if you could save you'll get just one file
With everything to Create page
And then when you go to open. Mhtml file you're probably find that the default is Internet Explorer on
Windows PC but you can also open in Chrome and you can either change the default because they open with
Dropping into a chrome window and it should open
That's it for the short video
Please check out the other videos from my channel water helpful tips and tricks
Or my website PC rajah.com
Thanks for watching we will see you next time