You notice people moving their head up and down
Especially
The farthest country
And heads are bobbling everywhere
Thank you have a nice day
Thank you thank you very much
Is it
Approval or false
The answer can be all of the above
It's so unique
That it deserves
Its own video explanation
The no wobble baby wobble
So what's up
The I understand wobble
Presents the most interesting thing that I find 100% subconscious
If you ask people to do it on the spot
They can't
Something more understanding that person
A slower head wobble is only a little understanding or just a sign of
Respect
This is just one of the many unique things about Indian culture